co-construct.com 2017-06-09

# Privacy Policy | CoConstruct

This Privacy Statement covers Co-construct, LLC, which is referred to as “we,” “us,” and “our” throughout this statement.

We are committed to protecting our customers’ information. In the course of providing a communication and project management tool related to construction, we need to collect and maintain certain nonpublic personal information. This Privacy Statement answers some questions about what nonpublic personal information we collect, what we do with it, and how we protect it.

### How do we protect the confidentiality and security of nonpublic personal information?

  * Access to account information is password protected.
  * Login information is encrypted using SSL technology.
  * We provide a “Log out” button which will terminate a user’s session, so that no future users on the same computer can access the password-protected areas of the service without logging in themselves.

We have in place physical, electronic and managerial procedures to protect the information we collect online. However, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the internet.

### What types of nonpublic personal information do we collect?

CoConstruct provides a platform where individuals may input information about a construction project, such as price, payment terms, and various decisions about the project. The CoConstruct platform also retains personal communications that users make in the site. To that end, any information that users choose to put into CoConstruct are collected by us.

We do not collect any personally identifiable information from visitors to our website unless such information has been voluntarily provided by the visitor. We may also collect your name and email address if you send electronic mail from the website. In addition to the above,we may also collect CoConstruct user information, account status, the IP address, type of browser and operating system of visitors to the website. We may also send to visitors who have supplied personal information, via regular mail or electronic mail, general information about CoConstruct and a description of its products and services. We will remove you from any such mailing list upon your request.

### What types of nonpublic personal information do we disclose?

We may disclose nonpublic personal information we collect for system troubleshooting, maintenance, and update purposes. Nonpublic personal information may also be disclosed as permitted by law or to cooperate with regulators or law enforcement authorities. We do not sell nonpublic personal information.

Our employees (for example, customer service personnel) and third party service providers have access to your nonpublic personal information only on a “need to know” basis.

### What should I know about “cookies”?

“Cookies” are small amounts of data that a website can send to your web browser and store on your computer. Cookies do not contain personal information about you, unless you knowingly provide it. Cookies can note that your browser was used to visit certain sites or pages.

We use cookies and website traffic statistics to help improve our website and services, to analyze repeat visits to our website, to analyze how visitors use our website, and to grant users access to password protected areas of the site.

### What can I do to help with online security?

In addition to our security measures, you can also take steps to maximize your security online and to protect your information, such as picking a password with a combination of upper and lower case letters, numbers, and symbols. You should also change your password on a regular basis and not share your login information with others.

### Policy Updates

Co-construct, LLC reserves the right to modify its policies at any time. Any modification is effective upon posting on our website. If you are a regular visitor to our website, we recommend that you check this Privacy Statement on a regular basis. By using our website, you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information in accordance with this Privacy Statement. If you do not agree to this Privacy Statement, please do not use this website.

_This privacy statement was last revised on 3/27/17._
